Guide to the Douglas Menuez Photography Collection MSS.PHOTO.0451
Dept. of Special Collections & University Archives
- Series 7. Accession 2008-179, 52.0 Linear feet
  - Subseries 4. Prints
    - Jaguar (Box 88, Folder 6)
    - Jaguar (Box 88, Folder 7)
      rolls: 25171-25176
    - Jaguar (Box 88, Folder 8)
      rolls: 25181-25189
    - Jaguar (Box 88, Folder 9)
      rolls: 25191-25209
    - Jaguar (Box 89, Folder 1)
      rolls: 25210-25219
    - Jaguar (Box 89, Folder 2)
      rolls: 25220-25227, 82929
    - Kellogg's (Flat-box 60, Folder 1)
    - Kid's Party (Flat-box 60, Folder 2)
    - Kodak Work Prints (Flat-box 60, Folder 3-4)
    - Kraft 2% (Box 89, Folder 3)
    - LAM (Flat-box 60, Folder 5-6)
    - Land's End (Flat-box 81, Folders 2-6)
    - LaSalle (Box 89, Folder 4)
    - Lindo, Delroy (Flat-box 60, Folder 7-10)
    - Lindo, Delroy (Flat-box 61, Folder 1-2)
    - Lindo, Delroy (Flat-box 81, Folders 7-8)
    - Lee, Eddy (Next, Inc.) (Flat-box 61, Folder 3)
    - L'Uomo Vogue (Flat-box 61, Folder 4)
    - L'Uomo Vogue (Box 89, Folders 5-6)
    - L'Uomo Vogue Scientists - John Aikin (Flat-box 61, Folder 5)
    - L'Uomo Vogue Scientists - Charles Carlson (Flat-box 61, Folder 6)
    - L'Uomo Vogue Scientists - D. Kent Cullers (Flat-box 61, Folder 7)
    - L'Uomo Vogue Scientists - Goery Delacote (Flat-box 61, Folder 8)
    - L'Uomo Vogue Scientists - Paul Doherty (Flat-box 61, Folder 9)
    - L'Uomo Vogue Scientists - Frank Drake (Flat-box 61, Folder 10)
    - L'Uomo Vogue Scientists - Thomas Humphrey (Flat-box 61, Folder 11)
    - L'Uomo Vogue Scientists - Lucio L. Lanza (Flat-box 61, Folder 12)
    - L'Uomo Vogue Scientists - Frank Millero (Flat-box 61, Folder 13)
    - L'Uomo Vogue Scientists - Wallace J. Nichols (Flat-box 62, Folder 1)
    - L'Uomo Vogue Scientists - Noel Wanner (Flat-box 62, Folder 2)
    - L'Uomo Vogue Scientists - Stanford E. Woosley (Flat-box 62, Folder 3)
    - L'Uomo Vogue Scientists - Doug Vakoch (Flat-box 62, Folder 4)
    - L'Uomo Vogue Scientists - Zane Vella (Flat-box 62, Folder 5)
    - Mac World (Flat-box 62, Folder 6)
    - MCDS (Flat-box 62, Folders 7-11)
    - MCDS (Flat-box 62, Folders 12-18)
    - MCDS (Flat-box 63, Folder 1)
    - Metlife, 1999 (Flat-box 63, Folder 2)
    - MIWI fashion & portraits (Box 89, Folder 7)
    - Mom & Son, 2000 BMW (Box 89, Folder 8)
    - Mom & Son, 2000 BMW - color (Box 90, Folder 1)
    - MSDW (Box 90, Folder 2)
    - My Year in the Wilderness (Flat-box 63, Folder 3-4)
    - Naked Ballet (Flat-box 81, Folder 9)
    - Naked Ballet (Flat-box 82, Folders 1-4)
    - Naked Ballet (Flat-box 82, Folders 5-10)
    - Naked Ballet (Box 90, Folder 3)
    - Neal White (Flat-box 63, Folders 5-6)
    - Newton (John Sculley) (Flat-box 63, Folder 7)
    - NEXT (Flat-box 73, Folder 4)
    - Nikon P700 (Flat-box 63, Folder 8)
    - Northwest Airlines (Flat-box 63, Folders 9-10)
    - Not for publication prints (Flat-box 64, Folder 1)
    - Nude couple portraits (92_100) (Flat-box 64, Folder 2)
    - Old prints/portraits (Flat-box 64, Folder 3)
    - Paoco School (Flat-box 64, Folder 4)
    - Paoco School (Box 90, Folder 4)
    - The Party - outs (Flat-box 64, Folders 5-6)
    - The Party (photocopy) (Flat-box 64, Folders 7-8)
    - The Party (Flat-box 65, Folder 1)
    - The Party (498-28) (Flat-box 65, Folder 2-5)
    - Photo albums (Box 90, Folders 5-6)
    - Piezography (Flat-box 83, Folder 1)
    - Planet Out (Box 90, Folder 7)
    - Portrait prints (Flat-box 65, Folder 6)
    - Portraits - miscellaneous (Flat-box 65, Folders 7-8)
    - Portraits - miscellaneous (Flat-box 66, Folder 1-2)
    - The Power of Women (Flat-box 66, Folders 3-7)
    - Proofs (Flat-box 83, Folder 2)
    - QVC (Flat-box 66, Folder 8)
    - Rat dog (Box 90, Folder 8)
    - Redford, Amy (Flat-box 66, Folder 9)
    - Reebok (Flat-box 66, Folder 10)
    - Reebok (Flat-box 83, Folders 3-4)
    - Reportage postcards (Box 90, Folder 10)
    - Samir 157 (Flat-box 67, Folder 1)
    - San Francisco Magazine selects, 2000 (Flat-box 67, Folder 2)
    - San Francisco Magazine, 2000 (Flat-box 67, Folders 3-7)
    - San Jose/San Quentin/Mexico (Flat-box 67, Folder 8)
    - Sapient (Box 90, Folder 11)
    - Saturn (Flat-box 67, Folder 9)
    - Saturn (Flat-box 68, Folders 1-4)
    - Saturn (Box 90, Folder 12)
    - Saturn (prints from photo essay on building Saturn cars) (Flat-box 68, Folder 5)
    - Saturn & Amanda (Flat-box 67, Folder 10)
    - Saturn & Amanda (Box 90, Folder 13)
    - Saturn outs (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - Second Date (Box 91, Folders 2-3)
    - SF center (Box 91, Folder 4)
    - SFO Airport - outs (Flat-box 68, Folder 6)
    - SFO Airport (Flat-box 68, Folders 7-10)
    - SFO outs (Box 91, Folder 5)
    - SFSU (Flat-box 68, Folders 11-13)
    - Silicon Valley - miscellaneous (Flat-box 68, Folder 14)
    - Silicon Valley - miscellaneous (Flat-box 69, Folders 1-3)
    - Small prints (black-and-white) (Box 91, Folders 6-7)
    - Small prints (color) (Box 92, Folder 1)
    - Smith & Hawkins (Flat-box 69, Folder 4)
    - Sports/Fashion (Flat-box 83, Folders 5-6)
    - Sports/Fashion (Flat-box 84, Folder 1)
    - Still lifes (Box 92, Folders 2-3)
    - Stock Races "B" (Flat-box 69, Folders 5-10)
    - Stock Races, 2000 September (Flat-box 69, Folders 11-12)
    - Stock Races (photocopies) (Flat-box 69, Folder 13)
    - Stock Races, 2000 September (Flat-box 69, Folder 14)
    - Submission (Box 92, Folders 4-6)
    - Tekronics Fash 1 output (Flat-box 70, Folder 1)
    - Tesao (Flat-box 70, Folder 2)
    - To Doug Menuez (Flat-box 70, Folders 3-4)
    - TransAm/Motrin/Meridith (photocopies) (Box 92, Folder 7)
    - TFI (Flat-box 70, Folder 8)
    - TFI (2nd prints for Eddie) (Flat-box 70, Folder 9)
    - TFI (2nd prints for Eddie) (Flat-box 71, Folder 1-2)
    - TFI (Flat-box 71, Folders 3-9)
    - Tequila - A selects - color (Flat-box 71, Folder 10)
    - Tequila - A Selects - Photo CD (Flat-box 72, Folder 1)
    - Tequila - B Selects - Color (Flat-box 72, Folder 2)
    - Tequila - B Selects - Photo CD (Flat-box 72, Folder 3)
    - Tequila - C Selects - Color (Flat-box 72, Folder 4)
    - Tequila - C Selects - Photo CD (Flat-box 72, Folder 5)
    - Tequila - selects and outs (Flat-box 72, Folders 6-7)
    - Tequila - miscellaneous (Flat-box 72, Folders 8-9)
    - Tequila - miscellaneous (Flat-box 73, Folders 1-2)
    - Weir, Bob (Box 93, Folder 1)
    - Wild (Box 93, Folder 2)
    - Wild (Flat-box 73, Folder 3)
    - Wilderness (Flat-box 70, Folder 5)
    - Wilderness (Flat-box 84, Folders 2-4)
    - Wilderness - notes (Box 93, Folder 9)
    - Women of Power (Flat-box 70, Folders 6-7)
    - Work prints (Box 93, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous color (Flat-box 73, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous photocopies (Box 93, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous photographs (Flat-box 73, Folders 6-11)
    - Miscellaneous prints (Flat-box 74, Folders 1-7)
    - Miscellaneous prints (Flat-box 75, Folders 1-11)
    - Miscellaneous prints (Flat-box 76, Folders 1-9)
    - Miscellaneous prints (Flat-box 77, Folders 1-5)
    - Miscellaneous prints (Flat-box 84, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous prints (Flat-box 85, Folders 1-6)
    - Miscellaneous prints/photocopies (Box 93, Folders 5-8)
- Series 8. Accession 2011-132, 47.5 Linear feet
  Arrangement note
  The original order of the materials as received from the donor has been maintained. CDs containing digital image files of Menuez's work have been housed in duplicate folders and placed in Subseries 2. Jobs - Electronic Media.
  This series contains slides, negatives, contact sheets and CDs (97) of Menuez's commercial work.
  - Subseries 1. Jobs
    This subseries contains slides, negatives and contact sheets of Menuez's commercial photography work. CDs containing digital images have been removed and placed in Subseries 2. Jobs - Electronic Media (CLOSED to researchers).
    - Willis and Geiger - Community Garden, 98.25.11 (edited 10.26), 1998 October (Box 1, Folders 1-3)
    - Willis and Geiger - Softball, 98.25.14 (edited 10.26), 1998 October (Box 1, Folders 4-5)
    - Willis and Geiger - Great White Hunter, 98.25.15 (edited 10.26), 1998 October (Box 1, Folders 6-7)
    - Willis and Geiger - Antique Cars, 98.25.16 (edited 10.26), 1998 October (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Willis and Geiger - Antique Cars, 98.25.16 (edited 10.26) (Box 2, Folders 1-2)
    - Willis and Geiger - Rowboat and Farmers Market, 98.25.17 (edited 10.26), 1998 October (Box 2, Folders 3-4)
    - Willis and Geiger - Father and Child, 98.25.17 (edited 10.26), 1998 October (Box 2, Folders 5-6)
    - Willis and Geiger - Safari West, 98.25.18 (edited 10.26), 1998 October (Box 2, Folders 7-9)
    - Willis and Geiger - Safari West, 98.25.18 (edited 10.26), 1998 October (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Willis and Geiger - Photographer, 98.25.19 (edited 10.26), 1998 October (Box 3, Folders 2-3)
    - Willis and Geiger - Gardener, 98.25.19 (edited 10.26), 1998 October (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Willis and Geiger - Horse at S. Brook Ranch, 98.25.20 (edited 10.26), 1998 October (Box 3, Folders 5-7)
    - Willis and Geiger - Vintage Cars, 98.25.21 (edited 10.26), 1998 October (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Willis and Geiger - Vintage Cars, 98.25.21 (edited 10.26), 1998 October (Box 4, Folders 1-2)
    - Willis and Geiger - Lake w/ Coffee, 98.25.22 (edited 10.26), 1998 October (Box 4, Folders 3-5)
    - Willis and Geiger - DM Selects, 98.25, 1998 October (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Willis and Geiger - Arm Wrestling, 98.25.3 (edited 10.26), 1998 October (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Willis and Geiger - Golf, 98.25.3 (edited 10.26), 1998 October (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Willis and Geiger - Golf, 98.25.3 (edited 10.26), 1998 October (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Willis and Geiger - Flag, 98.25.5 (edited 10.26), 1998 October (Box 5, Folders 2-3)
    - Willis and Geiger - Sailboat at the Dock, 98.25.5 (edited 10.26), 1998 October (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Willis and Geiger - Badminton, 98.25.6 (edited 10.26), 1998 October (Box 5, Folders 5-6)
    - Willis and Geiger - Scuba, 98.25.6 (edited 10.26), 1998 October (Box 5, Folders 7-8)
    - Willis and Geiger - BBQ, 98.25.7 (edited 10.26), 1998 October (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Willis and Geiger - BBQ, 98.25.7 (edited 10.26), 1998 October (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Willis and Geiger - Tennis, 98.25.8 (edited 10.26), 1998 October (Box 6, Folders 2-4)
    - Willis and Geiger - Mark Hopkins, 98.25.9 (edited 10.26), 1998 October (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Willis and Geiger - Marine Architect, 98.25.9 (edited 10.26), 1998 October (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Willis and Geiger - Chart Reader, 98.25.9 (edited 10.26), 1998 October (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Willis and Geiger - Cricket, 98.25.10 (edited 10.26), 1998 October (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Willis and Geiger - Cricket, 98.25.10 (edited 10.26), 1998 October (Box 7, Folders 1-2)
    - Willis and Geiger - Inverness Boat w/ Pole, 98.25.12 (edited 10.26), 1998 October (Box 7, Folders 3-6)
    - Willis and Geiger - Horse - Filoli, 98.25.13 (edited 10.26), 1998 October (Box 7, Folders 7-8)
    - Willis and Geiger - Post Hole Gig, 98.25.13 (edited 10.26), 1998 October (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Prince of Persia, 99.3 (DM Selects) (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Prince of Persia - Keane Advertising, 99.3, 1999 February (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Meredith - Saatchi and Saatchi, 97.12, 1997 August (Box 8, Folders 4-7)
    - Meredith, 97.12 (DM Selects) (Box 8, Folders 8-10)
    - Credit Suisse - Doremus, 99.6.1 (rolls 67353-67376), 1999 March (Box 9, Folders 1-3)
    - Credit Suisse - Doremus, 99.6.2 (rolls 67399-67448), 1999 March (Box 9, Folders 4-7)
    - Metlife, 99.20, 1999 July (Box 9, Folders 8-9)
    - Metlife, 99.20.2 (CD(s) removed and placed in duplicate folder in Subseries 2), 1999 July (Box 10, Folders 1-2)
    - Credit Suisse, 99.21, 1999 July (Box 10, Folders 3-4)
    - Altru Health System, 99.22.1, 1999 July (Box 10, Folders 5-9)
    - Altru Health System, 99.22.2, 1999 July (Box 11, Folders 1-4)
    - Pedestrian Safety - Goodby Silverstein, 00.700.0, 2000 July (Box 11, Folders 5-7)
    - Pedestrian Safety - Goodby Silverstein, 00.700.1, 2000 July (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Du Maurier - Barcelona - "Customs", 00.26.6, 2000 March (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Du Maurier - Barcelona - "Customs", 00.26.6, 2000 March (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Du Maurier - Barcelona - "Customs", 00.26.7, 2000 March (Box 12, Folders 2-4)
    - Du Maurier - Barcelona - "Field/Snow", 00.26.4, 2000 March (Box 12, Folders 5-7)
    - Gateway Learning/Hooked on Phonics (color), 1998 June (Box 12, Folders 8-9)
    - Southern Company SS&K Shot, 98.31, 1998 May (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Motrin - Saatchi & Saatchi, 98.10.2, 1998 January (Box 13, Folders 2-4)
    - Cisco/Med - Willis and Geiger, 99.5, 1999 March (Box 13, Folders 5-8)
    - Hallmark 99 cent cards - Leo Burnett - DM Selects, 00.18, 2000 February (Box 13, Folders 9-11)
    - Du Maurier - Barcelona - "Loft," 00.26.11, 2000 March (Box 14, Folders 1-2)
    - Du Maurier - Barcelona - "Field/Snow," 00.26.3, 2000 March (Box 14, Folders 3-5)
    - Corbis Image Submission, H03_014, Box 1 (CD(s) removed and placed in duplicate folder in Subseries 2) (Box 14, Folders 6-7)
    - Hallmark 99 cent cards - Leo Burnett (DM selects), Aphrodesiac (DM selects), 00.18.4, 2000 February (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Hallmark 99 cent cards - Leo Burnett (DM selects), Marriage Counselor (DM selects), 00.18.4, 2000 February (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Hallmark 99 cent cards - Leo Burnett (DM selects), Marriage Counselor (DM selects), 00.18.4, 2000 February (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Corbis Image Submission, H03_014, Box 1 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Corbis Image Submission, H03_014, Box 2 (Box 15, Folders 3-4)
    - Corbis Image Submission, H03_014, Box 3 (CD(s) removed and placed in duplicate folder in Subseries 2) (Box 15, Folders 5-6)
    - Corbis Stock Submission #3 - final submission paperwork (99_6 G-Tech) (CD(s) removed and placed in duplicate folder in Subseries 2) (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Corbis Stock Submission #3 - final submission paperwork (97_12 Meredith) (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Corbis Stock Submission #3 - final submission paperwork (98_25 Willis and Geiger) (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Corbis Stock Submission #3 - final submission paperwork (99_22 Altru Health) (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Corbis Stock Submission #3 - final submission paperwork (99_29 Petstore.com) (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Corbis Stock Submission #3 - final submission paperwork (00_043 Philip Morris) (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Corbis Stock Submission #3 - final submission paperwork (00_085 Microsoft) (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Corbis Stock Submission #3 - final submission paperwork (00_096 Microsoft B Central) (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Corbis Stock Submission #3 - final submission paperwork (00_118 Microsoft Agility) (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Corbis Stock Submission #3 - final submission paperwork (01_001 Microsoft Proj 2000) (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Corbis Stock Submission #3 - final submission paperwork (01_007 Microsoft LOB P2) (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Corbis Stock Submission #3 - final submission paperwork (01_052 Kraft) (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Corbis Image Submission, H03_014, Box 4 (02_007 DITLO Africa) (CD(s) removed and placed in duplicate folder in Subseries 2) (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Corbis Image Submission, H03_014, Box 4 (02_023 DITLO LA Drug Dealer) (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Corbis Image Submission, H03_014, Box 4 (91_100 DITLO Ireland) (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Corbis Image Submission, H03_014, Box 4 (94_100 North Pole Expedition) (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Corbis Image Submission, H03_014, Box 4 (98_15 Shanghai Bikes) (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Corbis Image Submission, H03_014, Box 4 (98_23 SF Airport) (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Corbis Image Submission, H03_014, Box 4 (CEO Portraits) (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Corbis Image Submission, H03_014, Box 4 (Favellas) (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Corbis Image Submission, H03_014, Box 4 (The Grateful Dead) (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Corbis Image Submission, H03_014, Box 4 (H00_084 Stock Car Races) (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Corbis Image Submission, H03_014, Box 4 (H01_008 The Basques) (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Corbis Image Submission, H03_014, Box 4 (H01_009 Ethiopia) (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Corbis Image Submission, H03_014, Box 4 (97_102 One Digital Day) (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Corbis Image Submission, H03_014, Box 4 (H01_010 Brazil) (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Corbis Image Submission, H03_014, Box 4 (Various Celebrities) (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Corbis Image Submission, H03_014, Box 5 (Willis and Geiger 98_25) (Box 16, Folders 16-17)
    - Corbis Image Submission, H03_014, Box 5 (99_3 Prince of Persia) (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Corbis Image Submission, H03_014, Box 5 (99_5 Cisco) (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Corbis Image Submission, H03_014, Box 5 (99.22 Altru Health) (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Corbis Image Submission, H03_014, Box 5 (99.29 Petstore.com) (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Corbis Image Submission, H03_014, Box 5 (00_017 Hallmark - Test) (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Corbis Image Submission, H03_014, Box 5 (00_018 Hallmark) (Box 16, Folders 23-24)
    - Willis and Geiger - Seaplanes, 98.25.1 (edited 10.26), 1998 October (Box 16, Folders 25-26)
    - Willis and Geiger - Sailboat, 98.25.2 (edited 10.26), 1998 October (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Willis and Geiger - Sailboat, 98.25.2 (edited 10.26), 1998 October (Box 17, Folders 1-2)
    - Willis and Geiger - Vintage Airplanes, 98.25.4 (edited 10.26), 1998 October (Box 17, Folders 3-5)
    - Willis and Geiger - Selects, S98.25.1 (Box 17, Folders 6-8)
    - Willis and Geiger - Studio Selects (DM selects), 1998 October (Box 18, Folders 1-2)
    - Hitachi - Doremus Advertising, 00.2 (DM selects) (CD(s) have been removed and placed in dupicate folders in Subseries 2), 2000 January (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Callaway - RMB Vivid, 00_45, 2000 May (Box 18, Folders 4-5)
    - Callaway Golf Apparel - Brian Boram/RMB Vivid, 00.45.1, 2000 May (Box 18, Folders 6-8)
    - Callaway Golf Apparel - Brian Boram/RMB Vivid, 00.45.2 (chrome), 2000 May (Box 18, Folders 9-10)
    - Callaway Golf Apparel - David Repyak Art Direction, 00.45.2 (breathable), 2000 May (Box 19, Folders 1-2)
    - Callaway Golf Apparel - David Repyak Art Direction, 00.45.2 (quick drying), 2000 May (Box 19, Folders 3-4)
    - Callaway Golf Apparel - David Repyak Art Production, 00.45.3, 2000 May (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Callaway Golf Apparel - David Repyak Art Production, 00.45.3 (UV protection), 2000 May (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Callaway Golf Apparel - David Repyak Art Production, 00.45.3 (timeless), 2000 May (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Callaway Golf Apparel - David Repyak Art Production, 00.45.3 (wrinkle-free), 2000 May (Box 19, Folders 8-9)
    - Callaway Golf Apparel - David Repyak Art Direction, 00.45.4 (finals - AD), 2000 May (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Callaway Golf Apparel - David Repyak Art Direction, 00.45.4 (finals - AD), 2000 May (Box 20, Folders 1-3)
    - Petstore.com, 99.29.1, 1999 September (Box 20, Folders 4-7)
    - Petstore.com, 99.29.2, 1999 September (Box 20, Folders 8-9)
    - Petstore.com, 99.29.2, 1999 September (Box 21, Folders 1-3)
    - Petstore.com, 99.29.3, 1999 September (Box 21, Folders 4-8)
    - Compaq FCB, 00.103.01, 2000 November (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Compaq FCB, 00.103.01, November 2000 (Box 22, Folders 1-3)
    - Emirates 02_019_01, St. Luke's Cinema, Mask (Ext. and Int), Trophy (DM Selects - Cinema), 2002 August (Box 22, Folders 4)
    - Emirates 02_019_01, St. Luke's Cinema, Mask (Ext. and Int), Trophy (DM Selects - Mask Ext.), 2002 August (Box 22, Folders 5)
    - Emirates 02_019_01, St. Luke's Cinema, Mask (Ext. and Int), Trophy (DM Selects - Mask Int.), 2002 August (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Emirates 02_019_01, St. Luke's Cinema, Mask (Ext. and Int), Trophy (DM Selects - Trophy), 2002 August (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Emirates 02_019_02, St. Luke's Restaurant, Fleet (DM Selects - Restaurant), 2002 August (Box 22, Folders 8-9)
    - Emirates 02_019_02, St. Luke's Restaurant, Fleet (DM Selects - Fleet), 2002 August (Box 23, Folders 1-2)
    - Emirates 02_019_03, St. Luke's Fisherman, Hotel (DM Selects), 2002 August (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Emirates 02_019_03, St. Luke's Fisherman, Hotel (DM Selects - Fisherman), 2002 August (Box 23, Folders 4-5)
    - Emirates 02_019_03, St. Luke's Fisherman, Hotel (DM Selects - Hotel), 2002 August (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Emirates 02_019_03, St. Luke's Fisherman, Hotel (DM Selects - Digital), 2002 August (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Emirates 02_019_04, St. Luke's, Trophy, 2002 August (Box 23, Folders 8-10)
    - Emirates 02_019_05, St. Luke's Hotel, 2002 August (Box 24, Folders 1-2)
    - Emirates 02_019_06, St. Luke's Restaurant, 2002 August (Box 24, Folders 3-5)
    - Emirates 02_019_07, St. Luke's Restaurant, 2002 August (Box 24, Folders 6-7)
    - Emirates 02_019_08, St. Luke's Mask (Int.), 2002 August (Box 25, Folders 1-3)
    - Emirates 02_019_09, St. Luke's Mask (Ext.), 2002 August (Box 25, Folders 4-6)
    - Emirates 02_019_11, St. Luke's Cinema, 2002 August (Box 25, Folders 7-8)
    - Emirates 02_019_11, St. Luke's Cinema, 2002 August (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Emirates 02_019_12, St. Luke's Fleet, 2002 August (Box 26, Folders 2-5)
    - Phillip Morris - The Bravo Group, 00.43 "Mom and Son" (color negative, M05100 parent print), 2000 May (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Phillip Morris - The Bravo Group, 00.43 "Mom and Son" (color negative, M05100 parent print), 2000 May (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Phillip Morris - The Bravo Group, 00.43 "Mom and Daughter" (color negative, M05100 parent print), 2000 May (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Phillip Morris - The Bravo Group, 00.43 "Mom and Daughters" (color negative, M05100 parent print), 2000 May (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Phillip Morris - The Bravo Group, 00.43 "Dad and Daughter" (color negative, M05100 parent print), 2000 May (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Phillip Morris - The Bravo Group, 00.43 "Dad and Daughter" (color negative, M05100 parent print), 2000 May (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Phillip Morris - The Bravo Group, 00.43 "Dad and Son" (color negative, M05100 parent print), 2000 May (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Phillip Morris - The Bravo Group, 00.43 "Dad and Son" (color negative, M05100 parent print), 2000 May (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Phillip Morris - The Bravo Group, 00_43_01 "The Parent Print", 2000 May (Box 27, Folders 1-3)
    - Phillip Morris - The Bravo Group, 00_43_01 "The Parent Print", 2000 May (Box 27, Folders 4-6)
    - Phillip Morris - The Bravo Group, 00.43.2 (chrome), 2000 May (Box 27, Folders 7-10)
    - Phillip Morris - The Bravo Group, 00_043_02 "The Parent Print", 2000 May (Box 27, Folders 11-12)
    - Phillip Morris - The Bravo Group, 00_043_02 "The Parent Print", 2000 May (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Phillip Morris - The Bravo Group, 00_043_02 "The Parent Print", 2000 May (Box 28, Folders 1-2)
    - Cisco Systems Inc. - Goldberg Moser O'Neil, 00.67.0 (CD(s) have been removed from this folder and placed in a duplicate folder in Subseries 2)., 2000 August (Box 28, Folders 3-5)
    - Cisco Medical, color slides, 99_005, 1999 March (Box 28, Folders 6-7)
    - Cisco, 99.5 (DM selects) (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Kraft 2 percent milk cheese, 01.052 - J. Walter Thompson, "Swimmers", 2001 October (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Kraft 2 percent milk cheese, 01.052 - J. Walter Thompson, "Swimmers", 2001 October (Box 29, Folders 1-3)
    - Kraft 2 percent milk cheese, 01.052 - J. Walter Thompson, "Skating", 2001 October (Box 29, Folders 4-5)
    - Emirates, 02_019_10 - St. Luke's Greek Fisherman, 2002 August (Box 29, Folders 6-9)
    - Discovery Channel, 98.21.1 (49251-49279), 1998 September (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Discovery Channel, 98.21.1 (49251-49279), 1998 September (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Discovery Channel, 98.21.2 (49227-49250), 1998 September (Box 30, Folders 2-3)
    - Discovery Channel, 98.21.3 (49320-49359), 1998 September (Box 30, Folders 4-5)